We've now reached the end of the section, and now you're all programmers.
So you can see we could basically stop now and you could go home and be done.
But I think there's a lot more that you can do.
There's a lot more to come and much more exciting things.
So you'll see as you get better and better in programming, programming, it gets more and more exciting
and more interesting.
So a quick recap on what we've done in this section.
We downloaded Python, downloaded wing, and we wrote our first program.
So so far you've learned one Python command print and you've seen the result down here.
As simple as that.
We also mentioned how you can reach out and get some help.
You will find environments like wing do have manuals and things and some sort of that.
There's even it'll bring you through to the Python manual that can also help you if you want, and even
to the Python website.
So a lot.
I also often look at the documentation for whatever language you're using.
So here if you actually just go and look at path and documentation, it explains quite well exactly
what everything does and how it's meant to be used again.
So a lot of the thing, even from installing the modules to tutorials etc., is here.
So that is another option of what you can do to find your way around.
So that's it.
You're at the end of this first section.
You've done extremely well.
You can go and just maybe rest for a couple of minutes and we'll see you back on the other side, because
it's going to start to get really exciting as we move on.